{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "to", "zoo", "they"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"tree\", Cardinal number in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"him\", List item marker in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "paw is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his _____________ and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["paw", "search", "mouse", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"go\", Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["zoo", "that", "take", "to"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Is \"a\", Pural plural Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "zoo is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["paw", "wagon", "zoo", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "idea is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"idea\", Superlative Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["that", "of", "after", "by"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: so", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["so", "and", "was", "of"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"in\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: paw", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["The", "let", "go", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"of\", Comparative Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["hunters", "later", "him", "captured"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"lion\", to in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Is \"a\", Predeterminer in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "The is Determiner", "question": "Is \"The\", Pural Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "was is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is \"was\", Wh-adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "later is Adverb", "question": "Is \"later\", Comparative Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "went is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is \"went\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["mouse", "paw", "wagon", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Is \"to\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tree", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Sometime", "captured", "tree", "few"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: Sometime", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["a", "him", "Sometime", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"that\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "captured is Verb (past participle)", "question": "Is \"captured\", Verb (past participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "being is Verb (present participle)", "question": "Is \"being\", Verb (present participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"lion\", Possessive pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"take\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "so is Adverb", "question": "Is \"so\", Possessive ending in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "zoo is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"zoo\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "was is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion _____________ so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["was", "tied", "went", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"search\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "paw is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"paw\", Verb (non 3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"him\", Coordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Is \"to\", Comparative Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went _____________ search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["by", "after", "in", "of"]}, {"explanation": "idea is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the _____________ of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["paw", "search", "zoo", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "his is Possessive pronoun", "question": "Is \"his\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"him\", Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "by", "of", "after"]}, {"explanation": "wagon is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"wagon\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["by", "him", "The", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: they", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["wagon", "take", "they", "search"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Is \"to\", WH-pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"mouse\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "tickled is Adjective", "question": "Is \"tickled\", Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "and is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"and\", WH-determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: captured", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past participle).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "to", "Sometime", "captured"]}, {"explanation": "let is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"let\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "and is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"and\", Possessive pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "able", "him", "the"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"by\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"of\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"After\", WH-determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: went", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["they", "to", "went", "in"]}, {"explanation": "few is Adjective", "question": "Is \"few\", Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["paw", "tree", "zoo", "wagon"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: The", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["mouse", "idea", "paw", "The"]}, {"explanation": "lifted is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is \"lifted\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the _____________ , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["tree", "mouse", "idea", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "able is Adjective", "question": "Is \"able\", Comparative Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Is \"a\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "they is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"they\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Is \"to\", to in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"that\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "help is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"help\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "hunters is Pural Noun", "question": "Is \"hunters\", Existential there in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is \"tied\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"him\", Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "he is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"he\", Existential there in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Is \"Sometime\", Superlative Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}], "success": 1}